Somewhere in Egypt is a big river called Denial, and often times we are in denial because we don't really want to admit what we're doing.
And that brings up, what is the definition of dating?
This is Dr. Paul, author of "Boomer Girls, a Boomer woman's guide to men and dating", and host of Ask Dr. Paul.
What is the definition of dating?
It's very simple, you're dating someone who is in your life.
If you're dating in general terms, than you're quote, unquote, dating.
You have a number of people that you're seeing.
By definition, dating means you're dating and seeing one person.
Seeing people means that you're going with people to different places, and with different people.
But dating, by definition, means that you're with one person, that you're seeing on a regular basis.
That, basically is dating.
Sometimes, as I said, people are in denial.
They are not really wanting to admit that, they are seeing other people, but that they're dating one person, when they're not.
Don't be in denial to yourself, and certainly don't be in denial to others.
Be honest, be totally up front.
Look, I'm seeing you, and I'm dating you, and I'm not seeing someone else.
Or, I'm seeing others, and I'm seeing you.
But you're not dating.
By definition, the definition is, if you're dating, you're dating some One, you're not seeing many people.
So, by definition, be it Merriam Webster, or anybody else's definition, it means being with a single person.
Whether you're male or female, that's what dating is defined as.
I'm dating this person.
This is Dr. Paul, may your fantasies of today, be your realities of tomorrow.